CURRICULUM VITAE

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Full name: DO BAO TRAM ANH

Date of birth: 27/10/1989

Mobile: 0918565827

Email: dobaotramanh@gmail.com

Address: Binh Loi Street, Binh Thanh District, Ho Chi Minh City



SUMMARY

I am a pharmacist who wants to challenge myself in the pharmaceutical business development area. Knowledge, experience, skills and enthusiasm are the most precious assets I can make a valuable contribution to pharmacy business activities.

Moreover, I would like to say I have a voracious appetite for learning new things, which allows me to quickly acquire product/service information and market intelligence. Besides, with good interpersonal skills, I can easily engage myself to different business environments. In addition, I always feel energetic to travel and stay on the field to exploit business opportunities. With all of these, I believe I can play a helpful role in the development process of many organizations.

EDUCATION BACKGROUND

University	University of Medicine and Pharmacy, Ho Chi Minh City 2014-2017				
Degree	Pharmacist				
Major	Pharmacy (University)				
Grade Point Average (GPA)	7.15/ 10				
Award	Credit				

Others

University	University of Agriculture and Forestry 2007-2011			
Degree	Bachelor			
Major	Biotechnology			
Grade Point Average (GPA)	8.0/ 10			
Award	Distinction			

Training course

Name of school/	University of Economics Ho Chi Minh City	
Organization	2011	
Specialization	Business administration	

LANGUAGE & COMPUTER SKILLS

Names of languages	Descriptions				
Vietnamese	Primary language				
English	TOEIC 710				

Computor deille	Degree B level Computer (excellent)		
Computer skills	Good at MS Word, Excel, Access, PowerPoint		

EXPERIENCES

Duration	Organization	Position and Responsibilities
	Name	
03/2018 - now	Rudolf Lietz Representative office	Position: Senior technical sales representative Responsibilities: - Be responsible for pharmaceutical ingredients (excipients). - Support technique about film coating system for tablets, excipients for direct compression and wet granulation, taste masking agent - Promote products to existing and new customer. - Maintain existing customers and improve business relationship. - Collect feedback of customer on products. - Prepare market, competitors, customers' reports on a regular basis.
		 Translating detailed product information into Vietnamese. Preparing product catalogue in Vietnamese.

10/2013 - 06/2017	BelAsia Representative office	Position: Sales executive Responsibilities: - Build relations with HCPs in hospital in HCM Prepare the Tender document - Translate protocol, preparing import documentation and other requirements to apply for import license - Responsibility for: • Prenatal screening kit and Neonatal screening kit • Elisa kit for diagnosis such as Malaria, Dengue, HSV, RPR, parasite • FISH kit for diagnosis of Genetics diseases • Manuka honey Dressing for Burn wound or necrotic wound
02/2012 - 09/2013	Tri Phuoc Biotechnology., JSC	Position: - Cell culture technician - Assistant production Manager Responsibilities in Cell culture technician position: - Keep cleanroom to meet the ISO cleanroom standards - Culture human adipose stem cells to provide for Viet Duc hospital in treating Spinal cord injury - Freezing human adipose stem cells, storing stem cells by cryopreservation technique - Thawing human adipose stem cells - Operate incubator, biosafety cabinet, microscope, water bath Responsibilities in Assistant product manager position: - Take part in writing standard operating procedures for company - Take part in writing content for catalogue and website of company
		 website of company Draft company introduction video script Prepare documents about application of stem cells in Orthopedics, Skin diseases, Neuron disease and Cosmetic Keep as archive files contact between Information department and the other department

12/2010 – 6/2011	Research Institute for Aquaculture No.2 (RIA2)	Position: Practical Student - Thesis title: Genetic diversity of red tilapia broodstock populations (Oreochromis spp.) using microsatellite markers Responsibilities: - Researching DNA, Microsatellite technology in Molecular lab - Doing PCR, Agarose gel Electrophoresis, Poly Acrylamide gel Electrophoresis technology
------------------	--	---

SOCIAL ACTIVITIES

- Green summer volunteer in 2008
- Traditional performance of Department of Biotechnology University of Agriculture and Forestry in 2007, 2008, 2009, 2010
- "I'm proud of being a student of University of Agriculture and Forestry" Competition in 2010 (third prize)

AWARDS

Names of achievements				Year attained			
Scholarship	to	encourage	studying	of	University	of	2008-2011
Agriculture a	Agriculture and Forestry						
Scholarship of Mobifone			2010				

REFERENCE

M.S Bui Thi Lien Ha

Department of Molecular Biology. Research Institue For Aquaculture No. 2 (RIA 2)

Mr. Duong Hai Nguyen

Product Manager. Tri Phuoc Biotechnology., JSC

Mr. Didier Verlinden

Director. BelAsia Headquarter